I come to the office of inquiry at de
Villiers, in that you people ask about this
health insurance policy, how to get the cream in it
and whom to approach, what is the
process, where to talk, whom to talk to, its
benefits, I will
make videos so that you can get all the details of the health insurance policy and you can get all the
documents at one place, I
promise I
will share with you all the details, Saurabh has done this on this channel,
for us my name is Bling and Chiku
and definition of planner and I am associated
with the insurance industry for the last fifteen years, you
and Jhanvi Kapoor bring videos in which
your partial of the
equator and good stitching can be done and
our tabloid is creating verification, so there are
two types of ATM process - cashless human
investment is safe, as soon as I found out that
today only I live cashless, so what happens, those who have taken a
policy from an insurance company,
many of their hospitals disappear, for example, if you have
taken a policy, then there you see
Fida Hussain Hospital Support,
1000 hospitals from Ujjain are on their networking sites
That if you
go to the office then you will not have to bother
with them, please plant
hospitalization, so that you can get the questions done
in the seat itself, you will
not have to pay any reimbursement, that is love, that is, by doing something,
only for minutes and we click on it, so
try this, you can check the network playlist, which suits
your personality and
where you are very soft, then you should
limit that, then you will have to know some romantic
documents, your policy,
which can help your health insurance policy and your
work, secondly I will
use here that many times it happens
that we have to go to the hospital, I do
not have a policy, if in an emergency
and I do not have a policy, then what do you do, then it
comes strongly suggested that you should have a
policy in an emergency bag,
which is in front of everyone, you should know
that you have a health insurance
policy and you can access it in case of an
emergency, secondly, nowadays in all the comments,
you have applications online, all those
insurance companies, then this application, so
I apply and register with your mobile number,
now do it there  If you
enter the entire policy details, then
how long have you had the
policy, how much has the policy benefit been,
how much pressure, everything with a Ruk
application, then the font will always be kept with you, so you have all the
details of a meeting in your phone
and you can easily share it, this is
cross pigmented, this is a third party
administrator dress, which does not do the body,
for your test from the insurance company, they
enter your details from you and get it done, they will
ask for the ID proof of the patient, they will make you face to face and
ask for the last solar policy and if you are treating someone, the
doctor will be all liquidated, the rest will be
coordinating the insurance company there
and now they will add it to them and they will get
all the documents from the insurance
company, the initial approval is from there, for the
first time so that your treatment is done,
then because what happens is that
when they
pull the leave, then they give the estimation that it is
activated, that the patient will be fasting
every day Shaheen and it is estimated that this much
expense will be incurred, there is no doubt, so
Select
Pushpa sentence and
start treatment by sending it to the insurance company. It is
approved by me. Final approval is given
when the treatment starts. At present, the
complete details, summary, all the bills,
everything is given to the insurance company by TPDS, TPA digits
and the time of his/her church. At
that time, the insurance company
approves it and after that
gives final approval. Every company has
different turnaround time. So,
reports are given in many different forums, minimum and maximum.
As soon as the documents are sent to the
hospital and obligation, the account is taken from there.
This point and on time,
Rohila comes within 24 hours. If something is worn, then
ask for insurance again. This
is pending or clarification on this,
two vacations are taken and PIN is set
etc., whatever has to be done at the
time of discharge, there are some of these all possible
items which are not covered in the insurance policy,
so the four patients who take the patients on those items will have to pay the fee to the
end university.
Suji decision is its process, so in this
modern and that you do not have any mean rule,
your policy is the hospital work and
your work is over in the insurance company's work, so that is why
I said that if
you get treatment done at such a place, then it should be
in their network list,
with whom their tyre reaches, they
also have a force on them, what is the purpose of getting a team, you
can get your PIN by taking injection, so the
whole journey is a vision that you
know this line hospitalization, we have to get him surgery for this thing,
you
already know, then you will inform the insurance company
first, then after
fitting in the same hospital, that doctor
or policy will give your stay, you will
give your policy in that hospital and the doctor will take it
and that insurance will be considered, if
I want to get a special treatment, then
call on this camp, Priya will come down a
day before, approval will be given to you, there is
no need to apply even then, the
fee increases for transmission, it is
not fixed seasonally, the seventh standard depends on a
different oil in between, so you
can get treatment within 10 days,
so you can also take it and keep it aside  It is
free and additional approval,
why not later, it is a control meter where
people face problems, for every investment,
RIMS alarm in minutes means that it will be done
on you, if you are referring to a network hospital, then
you will get it, then we will
collect it and only the
insurance will be put in it, so in this
box you have to collect the mode
switch, what are the things, first and most
important is that you should have everything original,
original, original receiver, your
originals, your medical test done,
report, everything, tips and be polite,
showroom cricket match may not be Hussain,
this year we have got it from our side because it will be a
duplicate or it will be a topic, then it
can be assumed that maybe you have got it from somewhere else, therefore if
you have a copy then
maintain the original in full size, if you want to watch this movie then
now we have to keep one more thing in
mind in this, you will understand that if it is
not in a network hospital then it is better to give it to the
insurance company that we are admitted
and with infinity wars of
condemnation it will not be made, then even this is hard
And it is not fast, you will not believe
that if they give international and it is better
for you only, then we will take the documents in the comment box, you will get
all your bills and this
channel, all respects, original, all medical
reports, whatever it is, then you will get
replacement, there are airplane funnels,
for reimbursement there are two ways, there is a
lot of your company,
Vikas Drop From, which is working online these days,
you can also login your claim digitally, if you
go on vacation, you
need to log in to their website, after clearing your claim, the process
starts there, you will get some major, take it down, I will
put it down, please I
know, and whose process I know, I will
put that balance below your bastard, by making a
deposit piece, if you are an obscene person, then you
can go to that link and type in the movie, some such yoga, then tell me the settings, what documents did you ask for,
wife events and you can assume that the
next month is big, copy of Aadhar and
quick from cancer, if you have to make the payment then
cream in cancelled cheque  If the printed neem neem
ginger is not printed then you
can put it in the bank statement of, here
all the IFSC code of your corporation is the
pride of this pimple and apart from that all the
documents that are there in your form, the
entire technique is yours,
you have put the bills, their receipt is
important, that means you take the bill from the hospital, if you have
stomach upset then a
few things are important for them, all the medical
reports, whatever messages were heard, reports,
diagnostic tests were done, they will put all of them,
along with this if you want to
prevent hospitalization, that
means before going to the hospital, if you had any
treatment due to which this fertilizer
came, then you can also apply for that free hospitalization
and even after that if
you were on that home care, were taking some treatment, were
taking medicines, were consulting
with a doctor, then you
can put the hospitalization in it and you will get that too, you
can press it once, so the limit of friends varies
in different policies, they can see
what is in your policy, then
reimbursement tax document  If it is complete then I don't
think so if the cake table is miscible
then it will not come Mesh that everything is
cut normally only once
and other problems which used to occur earlier, in
reality the shortage is never online, so by doing
153 you have to give all the documents and this
mark and all of them
go to them, if you want in the officer you
can get it back by requesting, your
problem is submitted,
take investment from us, so it has both the times,
so 2130 is the walking dead, that is the
central one of the company, that is
medium to torn walking dead, if there is any pending
insurance, we told you,
you should see this painting, it is in the comment
or we need additional information, then
please provide it, you will provide it,
then from there the time for the legs starts,
so in one to torn heels, so this was the
process of the team, if I have come then many things will be
forty, it is quite simple, it is not difficult, you have to
give all the documents in one go, for China
you need a little internet and  I was searching for it again and again, so add more
chillies so that the Chakli can be
checked along with it,
use it only once, if you need anything then I and my team are there
for you, our phone number and email ID are
not required, if you have any questions regarding Prince
or
questions of general, then you should ask them
in the comment section, I will try to
answer them completely, thank you very much
for watching this video and if
you have not subscribed yet then please
subscribe my channel and specific
[Music]